{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?",
      "correct_answer": "SpongeBob%20SquarePants",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Patrick%20Star",
        "Squidward%20Tentacles",
        "Mr.%20Krabs"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of the main character in 'Adventure Time'?",
      "correct_answer": "Finn%20the%20Human",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jake%20the%20Dog",
        "Princess%20Bubblegum",
        "Marceline%20the%20Vampire%20Queen"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which cartoon features a character named 'Homer'?",
      "correct_answer": "The%20Simpsons",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Family%20Guy",
        "Rick%20and%20Morty",
        "South%20Park"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the main character in 'Phineas and Ferb'?",
      "correct_answer": "Phineas%20Flynn",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ferb%20Fletcher",
        "Candace%20Flynn",
        "Perry%20the%20Platypus"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which animated series follows the adventures of a boy named Aang?",
      "correct_answer": "Avatar%3A%20The%20Last%20Airbender",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Teen%20Titans",
        "Ben%2010",
        "Danny%20Phantom"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Scooby-Doo', who is known for saying 'Scooby-Doo, where are you'?",
      "correct_answer": "Shaggy%20Rogers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fred%20Jones",
        "Daphne%20Blake",
        "Velma%20Dinkley"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the names of the two stepbrothers in 'Phineas and Ferb'?",
      "correct_answer": "Phineas%20and%20Ferb",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ferb%20and%20Isabella",
        "Candace%20and%20Ferb",
        "Phineas%20and%20Isabella"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which cartoon features a group of babies and their adventures?",
      "correct_answer": "Rugrats",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The%20Wild%20Thornberrys",
        "Hey%20Arnold%21",
        "Doug"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the nemesis of Bugs Bunny in many Looney Tunes cartoons?",
      "correct_answer": "Elmer%20Fudd",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Daffy%20Duck",
        "Yosemite%20Sam",
        "Porky%20Pig"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Cartoons",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of the underwater city in 'SpongeBob SquarePants'?",
      "correct_answer": "Bikini%20Bottom",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Krusty%20Krab",
        "Jellyfish%20Fields",
        "Rock%20Bottom"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
